ACWA Research Department Files 6240
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
ACWA Research Department Files
1960-1977
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
6240
0.5 cubic feet
0.5 linear ft.
Records.
6180097
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183> kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
R. Miles, August 27, 2009
EAD encoding:
Randall Miles, March 07, 2016
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: 5619: ACWA Records
Textile industry; Clothing trade; International labor activities; Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America; Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers Union; Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America. Research Department
6180097
- ACWA. Research Department. International Textile and Garment Workers' Federation. Comprehensive Materials. (folder 1), 1960-1964 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- ACWA. Research Department. International Textile and Garment Workers' Federation. Comprehensive Materials. (folder 1), 1960-1964 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- ACWA. Research Department. International Textile and Garment Workers' Federation. Comprehensive Materials. (folder 2), 1960-1964 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- ACWA. Research Department. International Textile and Garment Workers' Federation. Comprehensive Materials. (folder 2), 1960-1964 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- ACWA. Research Department. ILO Tripartite Technical Meeting for the Clothing Industry. Vol.1., 1964 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- ACWA. Research Department. ILO Tripartite Technical Meeting for the Clothing Industry. Vol.1., 1964 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- ACWA. Research Department. ILO Tripartite Technical Meeting for the Clothing Industry. Vol.2. (folder 1), 1964 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- ACWA. Research Department. ILO Tripartite Technical Meeting for the Clothing Industry. Vol.2. (folder 1), 1964 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- ACWA. Research Department. ILO Tripartite Technical Meeting for the Clothing Industry. Vol.2. (folder 2), 1964 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- ACWA. Research Department. ILO Tripartite Technical Meeting for the Clothing Industry. Vol.2. (folder 2), 1964 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- ACTWU. Men's Apparel: Tariff Exemption for Tokyo Round Negotiations., 1977 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- ACTWU. Men's Apparel: Tariff Exemption for Tokyo Round Negotiations., 1977 (Box 1, Folder 6)